Buhari Ahmed Alhassan

Kano 700320 buhari.alhassan0@gmail.com 08145044481

To be part of an organization where human development is of prior importance and to maximize potentials and professional expertise, to also be a competent and efficient worker as well as a team player contributing meaning to the overall growth and development of the community, and to use the knowledge, skills and experience of my study and other practical work and engagement, so as to contribute positively to a dynamic and extremely challenging environment through technology as well as to contribute generally to the development of the organization.

Work Experience

Core team member

Google Developer Student Club, Bayero University Kano Chapter 2019 to Present

IT department - Intern

9 mobile Nigeria - Kano August 2019 to January 2020

Responsible for both software and hardware troubleshooting

AD-HOC Assisting Presiding Officer

Independent National Electoral Commission 2019 to 2019

Full Sorter

7up Bottling Company plc 2012 to 2013

Classroom teacher

Manifest International School - KANO August 2011 to September 2012

Classroom teacher

Education

Undergraduate in Computer Science

Bayero University, Kano - Kano January 2017 to Present

Post-secondary (technical & vocational) in Computer Science

Kano State Polytechnic - Kano January 2015 to December 2016

Skills

- Angular 2+ (1 year)
- JavaScript (4 years)
- CSS (4 years)
- HTML (4 years)
- Git (2 years)

Links

https://github.com/makajeez

https://www.linkedin.com/in/buhariahmedalhassan